Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files A-E, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files
  - Subject Files E
    - Medgar Evers College (Box A-39, Folder 207)
      Also 2 velox prints. 1 print has a staple through edge. 2 prints have caption stapled to recto. 1 print has caption stapled to verso. Also multiple press releases and an invitation to a 1-28-1973 dinner-dance.
      Photographer if identified: Portfolio International, Dave Greene, King Photographers, Kilroy's Photo Studio
    - Medgar Evers College (Box A-39, Folder 208)
      Also one velox print. 1 print is a composite of two. Also one press release.
      Photographer if identified: King Photographers,
    - Medgar Evers College 86 Graduation (Box A-39, Folder 209)
    - Evers, Myrlie (Mrs. Medgar) (Box A-39, Folder 210)
      Photographer if identified: King Photographers, Nancy Crampton, Bill Powell, Jules Geller, Hairston Photo News Service, Dave Greene, Harris Photo
    - Evers, Myrlie (Box A-39, Folder 211)
    - Evers, Myrlie (Box A-39, Folder 212)
      Photographer if identified: Nancy Crampton,
    - Evers, Renee (Box A-39, Folder 213)
    - Evers, Rhett (Box A-39, Folder 214)
    - Eversley, Fred (Box A-39, Folder 215)
    - Eversley, Frederick W. Jr. (Box A-39, Folder 216)
    - Eversly, Linda (Box A-39, Folder 217)
    - Eversley, Lucille (Box A-39, Folder 218)
    - Everson, Darnella (Box A-39, Folder 219)
    - "Every Night When The Sun Goes Down" (Box A-39, Folder 220)
    - Everyman Fund Inc. (Box A-39, Folder 221)
      Also a sheet listing the holdings of Everyman Fund and 3 newspaper clippings.
    - Ewell, Richard (Box A-39, Folder 222)
    - Ewing, Geoffrey (Box A-39, Folder 223)
    - Ewing, Lorraine (Box A-39, Folder 224)
    - Patrick Ewing (Box A-39, Folder 225)
      1 slick with photo and stats. One halftone print. 1 newspaper clipping with photo. 2 prints have staples through edge.
    - Ewing, Patrick (Box A-39, Folder 226)
    - Ewing, Samuel D. (Box A-39, Folder 227)
      Photographer if identified: Ankers Capitol Photographers, Victor B. Greene
    - The Exceptions (Box A-39, Folder 228)
      Photographer if identified: L. St. Clair Dummett, A. Hansen Studio
    - Exclusive 13 (Box A-39, Folder 229)
    - Exhibits (Box A-39, Folder 230)
    - "Exorcist" (Box A-39, Folder 231)
    - Explainer (Box A-39, Folder 232)
    - Extreme Measures (Box A-39, Folder 233)
    - Exum, Charles (Mrs.) (Box A-39, Folder 234)
      Staple through edge of print. Print stuck to folder.
    - Exuma (Box A-39, Folder 235)
      Also one velox print and 1 internegative.
      Photographer if identified: Susanne Faulkner Stevens,
    - Ezell, Rhedes (Box A-39, Folder 236)
    - Ezema, Grace (Box A-39, Folder 237)